<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<books>
  <book>
    <name>fpt</name>
    <title><![CDATA[Capture Pricing <span class="helpCenter">eOffer Training</span>]]></title>
    <body><![CDATA[
      <div class='book_front_header'>
        <div class='main_banner_block'/>
      </div>
      <div class='book_front_body'>
        <h3>What is the New Capture Pricing Section?</h3>
        <p>Previously, you would enter pricing information using manual entry into a spreadsheet without a way to validate your information or check for errors.</p>
        <p>Now, with the Capture Pricing section, you will have three options for entering pricing data that provide a streamlined process spanning both eOffer and eMod.</p>
        <p>This new method offers a more intelligent pricing template that captures a more detailed picture of your pricing structure and provides feedback on the data you enter into the system, ultimately reducing errors in submission.</p>
        <div class='rate_block'/>
      </div>
    ]]></body>
    <content>
      <section>
        <name>formatted-pricing-tool-training</name>
        <title><![CDATA[Formatted Pricing Tool Training]]></title>
        <content>
          <page>
            <name>getting-started-tab-lesson</name>
            <title><![CDATA[Getting Started Tab Lesson]]></title>
            <body><![CDATA[
              <p>This is a lesson on filling out the <em>Get Started</em> tab. You must fill out this section before you can move onto the other tabs in the template. Click the play button to begin!</p>
              <div id="presentation" class="presentation_block">presentation/get_started_tab_lesson</div>
            ]]></body>
          </page>
          <page>
            <name>wizard-management-lesson</name>
            <title><![CDATA[Wizard Management Lesson]]></title>
            <body><![CDATA[
              <p>This is a lesson on completing the <em>Wizard Management</em> section. Click the play button to begin!</p>
              <div id="presentation" class="presentation_block">presentation/wizard_management_lesson</div>
            ]]></body>
          </page>
          <page>
            <name>special-charges-lesson</name>
            <title><![CDATA[Special Charges Lesson]]></title>
            <body><![CDATA[
              <p>This is a lesson on completing the <em>Special Charges</em> section. If you selected <strong>Yes</strong> to this section in <em>Wizard Management</em>, you will see it added to the left-hand navigation menu. Click the play button to begin!</p>
              <div id="presentation" class="presentation_block">presentation/special_charges_lesson</div>
            ]]></body>
          </page>
        </content>
      </section>
    </content>
  </book>
</books>
